nextmanagement.com 2019-04-06

# Next

We are Next Management LLC 16 Watts Street 6th Floor New York NY 10013 USA. Any references in this Policy to “we”, “our”, “us” etc. will be interpreted as a reference to us. Our contact details, can be found below under “Contacting us and making a complaint”.

Next Management is a modelling agency that represents talent across multiple geographical locations. We take privacy seriously and take all measures to keep your information secure.

We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Our privacy policy does not contain any surprises, although we ask that you read it carefully as it contains important information on who we are, how and why we collect, store, use and share your personal information, your rights in relation to your personal information and how to contact us.

We collect, use and are responsible for certain personal information about you. When we do so we comply with applicable data protection laws and we are the ‘data controller’ of your personal information.

This privacy policy relates to your use of our website at http://www.nextmanagement.com

Our website may contain links to third party websites. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy notice of every website you visit.

This website is not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children.

Our system hosts talent information provided to us by you (the talent) or your representative (a talent representative). We collect certain personal information about you when you use our website. Some of this personal information is collected directly, such as when you contact us or register with us or subscribe to our publications, and some is collected indirectly, such as your browsing activity while on our website (see ‘Cookies’ below)

Information that may be collected includes, but is not limited to, name (real or alias), email address, phone number, body dimensions, location(s) or availability and social handles. We allow the downloading of copyright pictures. This information about you is collected via computer forum and is stored in the backend system to be reviewed by agents. We also use third party mailing applications as well as API connectivity to a blogging server which hosts articles written by influencers.

We also collect new talent or recruitment information that is provide to us via the recruitment page. This information is inputted by you or an authorised third-party which can include your talent representative, manager or others. This information is sent to our recruitment division for further review that can result in a potential relationship with the agency.

When you contact us for information, we collect your name, email address and information in the correspondence between us.

When you browse our website, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.

[Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our business, our clients and other updates.]

We will use your information for the purpose of legitimate interests being pursued by us in relation to the services and products that we provide. For example, we will use your information for booking talent, sourcing talent, marketing and promotion. We will also use it to respond to any questions or concerns you have raised; for the operation of our website; to deal with administrative matters such as contacting you for business purposes; and (where applicable) to prevent fraud.

We may also provide marketing information to you in relation to our products where you have given your consent. If you do not wish to be contacted in this way, you can tell us by contacting us using the details set out at the end of the Privacy Policy or using the “unsubscribe” option in communications sent to you.

We may use your information in order to comply with any legal obligation that we have, in connection with any legal proceedings, or in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights.

Where you are located in the EU and we have relied on our legitimate interests to process your personal data, you may contact us to obtain more information, including in relation to our assessment of the impact on you.

Your information will be shared internally amongst our staff but they will only use it to carry out their duties in line with the purposes set out above. We will need to share your personal information with others from time to time, including:

  * our clients to book jobs and to collect content for potential bookings;
  * professional advisers, such as our accounting and legal advisers where they require that information in order to provide advice to us;
  * if we are required to do so by law or to a law enforcement agency;
  * if another entity acquires us or our assets, your information may be disclosed to that entity as part of the due diligence process and, if the acquisition goes ahead, your information will be transferred to that entity; and
  * our service providers who operate our website, or provide and support our management and data storage systems, including as set out below.

**Third party services**

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

We share information when this is required under the terms of our contract with client, booking agents request data and users visiting the site download data.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies, so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

**Links**

When you click on links on our Website, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

**Google analytics:**

We use Google Analytics to help us learn about who visits our site and what pages are being looked at.

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

Our website is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption and all users who have access to the backend systems sit behind firewalls and can only access backend data via SSH. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

We use a combination of software and hardware to achieve this level of security. The systems are monitored and maintained daily and all measures are taken to mitigate any data loss or breach.

Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to consent to cookies or not.

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

Your personal data will be stored and backed up by us and our suppliers on servers located outside of the European Economic Area (EEA) – specifically in the USA. All of the data captured is stored in servers within the UNITED STATES all servers are secure and protected by antivirus and firewalls. We transfer your personal data outside the EEA when you are located in the EEA and we enter into a contract with you. For all other transfers of personal data from outside the EEA, we will obtain your explicit consent. In deciding whether to grant your consent for such transfer outside the EEA, you should bear in mind that the countries to which your personal data may be transferred, may not have the level of safeguards in relation to the processing of personal data as those in the EEA.

We only keep your information for as long as is reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy and to fulfil our legal obligations.

In summary, however, we keep:

  * Information about contact details for as long as is necessary for the processing purpose(s) for which the data was collected, and any other permissible, related purpose.
  * Information about your visits to our website for 365 days.

We will securely erase your information in advance of these deadlines if we decide that we no longer need it.

Where you are located in the EEA, you have the following rights regarding your information:

**Rights**

| 

**What does this mean?**  
  
---|---  
  
Right to be informed

| 

You have the right to be provided with clear, transparent and easily understandable information about how we use your information and your rights. This is why we are providing you with the information in this Privacy Policy.  
  
Right of access

| 

You have the right to obtain access to your information (if we are processing it), and other certain other information (similar to that provided in this Privacy Policy).  
  
Right to rectification

| 

You are entitled to have your information corrected if it is inaccurate or incomplete.  
  
Right to erasure

| 

This is also known as ‘the right to be forgotten’ and, in simple terms, enables you to request the deletion or removal of your information where there is no compelling reason for us to keep using it. This is not a general right to erasure; there are exceptions.  
  
Right to restrict processing

| 

You have rights to ‘block’ or suppress further use of your information. When processing is restricted, we can still store your information, but may not use it further. We keep lists of people who have asked for further use of their information to be ‘blocked’ to make sure the restriction is respected in future.  
  
Right to data portability

| 

You have the right to obtain and reuse your personal data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format in certain circumstances. In addition, where certain conditions apply, you have the right to have such information transferred directly to a third party.  
  
Right to withdraw consent

| 

If you have given your consent to anything we do with your personal data, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time (although if you do so, it does not mean that anything we have done with your personal data with your consent up to that point is unlawful).  
  
To exercise any of these rights at, any time, you can contact us using the details set out at the end of this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If you would like to contact us, please contact our Privacy Compliance Officer via email at [Vancho@nextmanagement.com](mailto:vancho@nextmanagement.com)

Or call or write to us at:

Next Management NY: +1-212-925-5100 - 15 Watts Street, 6th Floor, New York, NY 10013

Next Management London: +44-207-251-9850 - Ground Floor Blocks B and C, Morelands Building, 5-23 Old Street, London, England EC1V9HL

Next Management Paris: +33-1-53-45-13-00 - 9 Boul. de la Madeleine, Paris, France 75001

Next Management Milan: +39-02-303-50-21 - 40, Via Filippo Turati, Milano, Italy 20121

Next Management Los Angeles: +1-323-782-0010 - 8447 Wilshire Blvd, Penthouse Beverly Hills, CA 90211

Next Management Miami: +1-305-531-5100 - 1688 Meridian Ave, Suite 800, Miami Beach, FL 33139

Next Management Toronto: +1-416-603-4807 - 777 Richmond St West, Suite 2029 Toronto, Ontario M6J 0C2

Next Management Montreal: +1-514-288-9216 - 1260 University, 4th FI, Montreal, Canada H3B 3B9

If you are in the European Union and are not satisfied with our response or you believe our use of your information does not comply with data protection law, you can make a complaint to the supervisory authority responsible for the territory in which you are located.
